[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The crew of which Apollo mission spent the longest time on the Lunar surface?", "correct_answer": "Apollo 17", "incorrect_answers": ["Apollo 9", "Apollo 7", "Apollo 12"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chocolate syrup was used as fake blood in the famous shower scene in the 1960 movie Psycho.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these characters was cut from the film The Crow, after being initially storyboarded?", "correct_answer": "Skull Cowboy", "incorrect_answers": ["The Devil", "Grim Reaper", "The band Hang Mans Joke"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress portrayed Hana, the French-Canadian nurse who looked after a critically burned man in the Oscar-winning movie The English Patient?", "correct_answer": "Juliette Binoche", "incorrect_answers": ["Kristin Scott Thomas", "Catherine Deneuve", "Audrey Tautou"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 2 prominent actors did the movie Colors star?", "correct_answer": "Sean Penn and Robert Duvall", "incorrect_answers": ["Sean Penn and Robert De Niro", "Dennis Hopper and Heath Ledger", "Robert Duvall and Aidan Quinn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the last human city on the planet in the 2003 movie The Matrix Reloaded?", "correct_answer": "Zion", "incorrect_answers": ["Xerx", "Eden", "Seraph"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does the love story end in Romeo Must Die ?", "correct_answer": "The two characters embrace and walk away", "incorrect_answers": ["The couple gets married", "Aaliyahs and Jel lis characters are killed", "Aaliyah and Jet Li kiss"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the western High Noon, after several minutes of shooting, Will Kane has killed two of Millers three henchmen. Who kills the last one?", "correct_answer": "Amy", "incorrect_answers": ["Will", "Miller", "Judge Henderson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What physical property of the diamond do carats measure?", "correct_answer": "Mass", "incorrect_answers": ["Purity", "Cut", "Color"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the speed of light in vacuum?", "correct_answer": "300 000 km/s", "incorrect_answers": ["500 000 km/s", "200 000 km/s", "400 000 km/s"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What commonplace object has parts called stretcher, runner and rib?", "correct_answer": "Umbrella", "incorrect_answers": ["Underwear", "Underlay", "Urn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you were taking a course in entomology, what would you be studying?", "correct_answer": "Insects", "incorrect_answers": ["Rocks", "Snakes", "Mold"]}]